<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Yuan Du&#39;s test website</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Yuan Du&#39;s test website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Awesome data science presentations and hands on references</title>
      <link>/2019/08/16/tools-reference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/08/16/tools-reference/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I searched a few pretty cool tools for R-based hands-on references.
 R Presentation Themes
 Why uses R presentation?
 Take advantage of R Markdown. You can write all your slides in Markdown text Power of interchange. You can include chunks of R code and rendered output like plots, results, tables, etc. in your slides Version control and sharing. You can use git for version control and share your GitHub repository  My current favorate Xaringan nanja-theme developed by Emi Tanaka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My journey of being research statistician</title>
      <link>/2019/07/30/my-journey-of-being-research-statistician/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/07/30/my-journey-of-being-research-statistician/</guid>
      <description>Curiosity
I&amp;rsquo;ve been always a person with a curious mind that constantly seaerches and looks things around. The wonder of history and the future, questionning on information on the insight drives me to the field of Statistics. I didn&amp;rsquo;t choose this field but accidentally inspired to be in the field. It was difficult for me to understand all the mathmatics and it&amp;rsquo;s still difficult till this day. But the more I know, the better I understand that how much I don&amp;rsquo;t know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tidy Text Mining</title>
      <link>/2019/07/18/tidy-text-mining/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/07/18/tidy-text-mining/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to the short course at SDSS 2019, I learned how to do tf-idf to topic modeling and sentiment analysis by using tidytext taught by Julia Silge, author of Text Mining with R and Mara Averick. They did a great job on teaching the four hour class. I didn’t expect to have so much covered in the short course.
Here is an example that I used the method to analyze A Tale of Two Cities and Great Expectations by Charles Dickens by using sentiment analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publish R blogdown by Netlify</title>
      <link>/2019/07/12/create-and-pushlish-rblogdown-by-netlify/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/07/12/create-and-pushlish-rblogdown-by-netlify/</guid>
      <description>I’m a noobie on using Github and Hugo. 😊 It took me quite a while to figure out how to use version control on Github through Rstudio. In this blog, I would like to share my obstacles on publishing website to Github and deploying my website by Netflify. Some of the obstacles were caused by not understanding the structure and workflow of Github/Blogdown because I took a shortcut by googling and trials &amp;amp; errors and didn’t have patience to read all the details of the Yihui’s excellent guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create your own logo and apply to your own website</title>
      <link>/2019/07/07/create-your-own-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/07/07/create-your-own-logo/</guid>
      <description>I have no background of editing html and css. It took me a while to figure out how to modify the Hugo Lithium theme for my own blog. so I would like to share it with you, by no means that this is the only way to do it.
Step 1: Generate your own favicon ico by using free favicon generator. I generated it by using my inital of my first name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My purr friend</title>
      <link>/2019/07/07/my-cat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/07/07/my-cat/</guid>
      <description>Meow there!
My name is Sissi, female, shorthair. This is silly me:
You may find me on my mommy&amp;rsquo;s Instagram</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R Markdown Introduction</title>
      <link>/2019/07/07/r-markdown-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/07/07/r-markdown-introduction/</guid>
      <description>R MarkdownThe first time that I used R Markdown was back to 2014 when I was in graduate school. Unfortunately, I haven’t used this as much as I would like to due to the inconvinience with IT in the hospital. I’m slowly trying to use Rstudio more and more as SAS has limited options on some analysis. R markdown is great for documenting R code and math expressions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>